Bubblewire live on bubblewire.xyz
One real-time feed for Twitch, X, and Kick.
The hook: real source-labeled flow
Live Twitch chat and X filtered-stream posts share one operator feed.
Every row keeps provenance
Select a message to inspect the raw normalized payload and proof receipt.
Search and source filters
Keyboard-first filters highlight signal without losing the room.
Author drill-down
Click an author to isolate context; Esc clears the view.
Watchlist alerts
Terms flag matching rows and raise toasts before moments scroll away.
Volume, heat, and themeable signal
Tape, radar, and heat rails expose bursts before you read every line.
Setup is honest
Green means proven; env values are booleans only, never secrets.
OBS overlay configurator
Tune max messages, fade, alignment, scale, and source filters.
Bubblewire: the moment, the proof, the broadcast
Live at bubblewire.xyz.